sandburg.edu 2019-06-24

# Privacy Notice

### Privacy Notice

At Carl Sandburg College (“the college”), your privacy is very important. This privacy notice covers the use www.sandburg.edu.

#### Information We Collect

  * When you interact with the college though www.sandburg.edu, such as filling out request more information forms (RIFs), we request basic contact information and may request additional information about your high school.
  * Sandburg uses common Internet technologies, such as cookies and web beacons to track interactions with the Sandburg website and emails.

#### Google Analytics and Online Advertising

Sandburg uses Google Analytics, which is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google places a cookie on the web browsers of visitors to www.sandburg.edu and collects, tracks and examines the use of www.sandburg.edu to prepare reports on site’s activities through Google Analytics dashboards and to share with other Google services the college subscribes to such as Google AdWords. Google also uses third-party audience data such as age, gender and interests to help us better understand the behavior of our website visitors.

This allows us to track and manage the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.

In addition, the college may use Google AdWords. The college may use Google AdWords and other third-party vendors for remarketing/retargeting. Google and remarketing/retargeting systems place cookies and/or web beacons on web browsers to serve ads based on your interests and/or past visits to www.sandburg.edu

Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Personal data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA. Find Google’s  _[privacy policy here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)_.

#### Use of Information Collected from Sandburg.edu

The information the college collects may be used to correspond with you. The college will never sell the personal information you submit to us through sandburg.edu to any persons or organizations. The college may share it with reputable third parties contracted to provide services such as email, or when required by law for the investigation of illegal or criminal actives, the exercise of legal rights or in defense against any legal claims, or otherwise. The college also maintain adherence to Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act regulations. For further information regarding how the college collects and uses all data please follow the link to the _GDPR Statement_ and the Carl Sandburg College _Privacy Policy_.

#### Opting Out

You may opt out of the third-party ad networks’ use of cookies by visiting the consumer opt-out page for the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising and edit or opt-out of Google cookie use by updating your preferences in the Ads Preferences Manager
